ICICI Lombard has come up with a new plan
called Elevate. If you
look at its symbol, it is also
Infinity, which you will get unlimited.
Infinity is a very different plan. If you compare all the best plans
of all the health insurance companies till date, then
this is such a plan
where this plan has
left every plan behind. Your
Infinity is that you
can take unlimited sum insurance from the company as many times as you want. Suppose you
took a policy of Rs. 10 lakh, if Rs. 10 lakh is exhausted, you will
get Rs. 10 lakh again. If Rs. 10 lakh is exhausted,
you will get Rs. 10 lakh again. So you
can take unlimited sum insurance from the company as many times as you want in
the same year. Fourth is Infinity,
you get unlimited bonus.
Here you will get unlimited bonus in which the
company will give you 100% bonus every year and this 100%
increase will keep on increasing, there is no stopping it.  So
this infighting is
your jump start
option, in this it means that if there is
any pre-existing problem, what is pre-
established,
now we start our video,
first I would like to tell you about myself,
my name is Amandeep Singh,
I have a total of five years of experience,
here you will get information about comparisons of all types of insurance, be it
health insurance,
life insurance, motor insurance,
plus if you are new to my channel, then
you can subscribe to the channel whose name
is Fines with Aman, from here we
start our video, here first of all
we talk about your entry age, the first thing is what is your entry age, at
what age will I get the policy, minimum age should be 18 years, maximum age will be
covered up to 125, if you are between 18 to 125 years
then you can take this plan, second
thing you can take this policy for one year, two years, three years, on
taking it for two years and three years
you get additional discount, long
term discount which is  Your third
thing here is what are the sum in shorts
available here, you will get the coverage you will get, the
coverage sum in short is one,
sometimes I say sub insurance, sometimes I
say coverage, it means the same thing, it
starts from 5 lakhs, 5 lakhs, 7 lakhs, 10 lakhs, 15 lakhs, 20 lakhs, 25 lakhs,
50 lakhs, 1 crore, 3
crores, this is your unlimited sum in shot, this is such a
sum in shot where no company is offering it right now,
but in this company you will get
unlimited sum in shot, so don't
worry about the coverage, if you are
looking at a family policy, then
you can add two adults and three children in the policy, the
child will
remain covered under the same policy for a maximum of 30 years, there will be no
problem, you will
get a single private AC room in the policy, there is
no limitation, you can take a private room
in the hospital, the second thing is day
treatment, day treatment means in which
we do not need to get admitted in the hospital, we
go for five to seven hours and get the
treatment done, every company has it  There is a
list and some companies do
not even provide the list, then they cover all day
care, so here all day care,
your surgeries are covered, ice treatment,
Ayurvedic, Siddha, Homeopathic
treatment etc. in which your Ayurvedic
treatment, Unani, Siddha,
Homeopathic treatment, these are your
treatments, these are also covered up to sum in short, the
day treatment that I told you earlier is also covered up to sum
in short, now let us talk about
domicile treatment, here that is
also covered up to sum in short, domicile
treatment means if bed
is not available in the hospital or the doctor has said
that you should take treatment at home, your condition is
such that you cannot come to the hospital or there
is a curfew condition outside, then you should
take treatment at home, the treatment must be for three days, then the
company will give you the full
claim up to sum in short, road ambulance, road
ambulance is also covered by the company here,
the most important thing is that this road is
covered up to sum in short, the
company has not kept any limit,
basic surgery is also covered in road ambulance  Meaning,
your surgery for obesity is also covered under the policy.
You can claim for it after two years of taking up to sum of rupees. The
refill benefit which I
told you in the beginning is unlimited time. You
can take coverage from the company. Let me tell you how, for example,
you took a policy of ₹ 10 lakhs and
you exhausted it within the same year. You have another
claim and you have to
claim again and you need the same ₹ 10 lakhs
or even a little less amount, then the
company will give you that
amount again as much as you need. What does it mean that the company will give you as much coverage as you want. Suppose
you are taking a policy of ₹ 10 lakhs, then ₹
10 lakhs gets exhausted in a year, you will get ₹ 10 lakhs again, if it gets
exhausted then you will get ₹ 10 lakhs again, if it gets exhausted then you will get ₹ 10 lakhs again,
in the same year you can take ₹ 10 lakhs from the company unlimited times. Guaranteed
cumulative bonus, you mean the
bonus which is inbuilt in the policy is covered.  It
starts at 20 and goes up to a maximum of 100%. For example,
you have taken a policy of 10 lakhs, next year it becomes 12 lakhs, then 14 lakhs,
16 lakhs, 18 lakhs, 20 lakhs. Now,
I told you in the beginning that the
bonus you are getting here is 100%. I will
tell you the points in Infacil, so you
must watch the video till the end. There are many
inbuilt features which
are covered in the policy. Now let us talk about advances. There are
many advances in this policy.
So the first point is that you have
paid money to the company for Infacil
here, but the company will give you the entire 50 lakhs
in one go. This feature is
not available in any other company. But keep one more thing in
mind, here the company will
give it to you only once in your lifetime. The
second add-on is your power
booster. As I told you in the beginning, the
company will increase your coverage amount by
100% and it keeps increasing.
This is a benefit that no other company
in the entire health insurance industry
is offering you, and no
one is offering it until 2024. You might
see it coming, but as of now,
this benefit is covered under this plan,
which means that your policy will continue to
increase 100% if you
add this rider. The
third point in the policy is your Jump Start. This
means that if you have a pre-existing
disease, the company will pre-register you.
If you already have one, the company will pay you the claim
for this after 30 days. The
next point in the policy is
your Claim Protector. Claim
Protector means non-payable items like masks,
etc., the company
covers that too up to a sum of Rs. Next is your
Domestic Air Ambulance. If you want an
Air Ambulance to be
covered in your policy, you can add this rider.
This is also covered up to a sum of Rs. 100 in the
policy.
Your maternity is also covered under the policy.
Plus, if we talk about
when is maternity covered, because in most insurance companies there is a
waiting period of three to four years,
but in this policy your
waiting period is of two years. If you
feel that two years is too much, then you
can add a rider. There is a rider in it in
which you can bring your two-year waiting period by
one year. For maternity coverage,
if you want maternity coverage to be
covered sooner than two years, then
you can get it covered after one year. If you have to add a rider, then
your insurance will be covered under the policy.
If you want, you can also reduce your premium under this policy by making a
payment. In this, you get the option of 10, 20, 30, 40, 50,
that you can
reduce your premium. So now let's
talk about waiting periods here.
Your waiting period for accidental
is covered from the same day, normal and critical incidents,
if you have a claim for anything.  If you need to get a
new plan or there is any problem
for anything, then it is covered in your policy
after 30 days. Your third point is
your specific surgery. There are 14 to 15
such surgeries which the insurance
covers after two years. If it is covered after 2 years, then it
is covered in your policy. Plus,
if you already have any problem, then the
insurance company will cover it after three years.
Regarding discounts,
some discounts are available in this policy.
Credit score: You
can avail a discount of up to 15% under this policy.
Credit score is an option for you, in which you can avail a
discount of up to 15%. This
discount is your 10-year discount. If
you take a policy for 2 years or 3 years, then
you will get an additional discount on it. You will get a discount of 10% on a 2-year
policy.
You will get a discount of up to 15% on a 3-year policy. And
if you compare this with other companies, then it is
more. This third discount is your
early renewal discount.  Early Renewal
Discount: You will get a discount of 2.5% in this,
meaning for example, you have
run the policy for a year now but your policy
renewal is about to come and
you still have one month left for the renewal, so here
if you renew the policy a month in advance,
you will get an additional discount of 2.5%.
Next is your wellness
discount, as I told you that
you get a discount up to 30% on renewal.
I told you in the beginning,
this means that you walk 10,000 steps per day.
These 10,000 steps
earn you some points, so on the
basis of those points, you can get a discount of up to 30% at the
time of renewal within the policy. So this was your complete
plan, IIC Lunt's Elevate Plan in
final it. So, till here, if you have any doubt, then
comment me in the comment box,
I will definitely try to answer you there.
And if you
want to take this health insurance policy here,
then you can contact me.  You can,
my mobile number will be in the description,
okay, and as far as any kind of
doubts are concerned, you can also call, plus if
you want to ask any query, you
can also call or you
can also comment in the comment box, plus if you
liked my video, even if you have
watched my video completely, then you should follow my channel
whose name is Finance with
Aman, so we will meet like this in the next video, bye bye